Register of the Poland. Ministerstwo Spraw Zagranicznych Records, 1919-1947.
Hoover Institution Archives
- SERIES NO. 323. PRESS REPORTS
  - 1943
    - America, North
      - United States (Box 167)
        - Diplomatic representations. Reports
          - Consulates
            - Chicago
            - Jan.-June (Folder 1)
            - July-Dec. (Folder 2)
            - Detroit
            - General (Folder 3)
            - Jan.-June (Folder 4)
            - July-Nov. (Folder 5)
            - New York
            - Jan.-June (Folder 6)
            - July-Dec. (Folder 7)
            - Pittsburgh
            - Jan.-June (Folder 8)
            - July-Nov. (Folder 9)
            - San Francisco (Folder 10)
          - Embassy
            - Jan.-Feb. (Folder 11)
            - March-Apr. (Folder 12)
            - May-June (Box 168, Folder 1)
            - July (Folder 2)
            - August (Folder 3)
            - September (Folder 4)
            - October (Folder 5)
            - November (Folder 6)
            - December (Folder 7)
        - Ministry of Defense. Press disputes in Detroit between Dziennik Polski and Centralny Komitet Obywatelski. Photocopies (Folder 8)
        - Polish-American press. Clippings. Photocopies (Folder 9)
    - America, South (Box 169)
      - Argentina
        - General (Folder 1)
        - Curitiba Consulate
          - Bulletin, February (Folder 2)
          - Clippings (Folder 3)
          - Reports (Folder 4)
        - Rio de Janeiro Legation. Reports (Folder 5)
      - Chile (Folder 6)
      - Colombia (Folder 7)
      - Mexico (Folder 8)
      - Peru (Folder 9)
    - Asia. China (Folder 10)
    - Australia and New Zealand
      - Australia (Folder 11)
      - New Zealand (Folder 12)
    - Europe
      - Czechoslovakia (Folder 13)
      - Finland (Folder 14)
      - France. Reports
        - January (Folder 15)
        - July (Folder 16)
        - October-December (Folder 17)
      - Germany (Folder 18)
      - Great Britain (Folder 19)
      - Ireland (Folder 20)
      - Italy (Folder 21)
      - Lithuania (Folder 22)
      - Portugal (Folder 23)
      - Romania (Folder 24)
      - Slovakia (Folder 25)
      - Spain (Folder 26)
      - Sweden (Box 170)
        - General (Folder 1)
        - Legation's bulletin (Folder 2)
        - Monthly reports
          - General issues, June-July (Folder 3)
          - January (Folder 4)
          - February (Folder 5)
          - March (Folder 6)
          - April (Folder 7)
          - May (Folder 8)
          - June (Folder 9)
          - July (Folder 10)
        - Polish-Soviet relations (Folder 11)
        - Reports on
          - Baltic States (Folder 12)
          - Eastern Europe (Folder 13)
          - Finland (Folder 14)
          - Nordic states (Folder 15)
          - Poland (Folder 16)
      - Switzerland (Box 171)
        - Press bulletin, Nov.-Dec. (Folder 1)
        - Reports
          - Jan.-March (Folder 2)
          - Apr.-May (Folder 3)
          - Aug. (Folder 4)
      - Turkey. Reports
        - Jan.-Apr. (Folder 5)
        - May-Aug. (Folder 6)
        - Sept.-Nov. (Folder 7)
      - Vatican (Folder 8)
    - Middle East
      - Egypt (Folder 9)
      - Iran (Folder 10)
      - Iraq (Folder 11)
      - Palestine. Consulates
        - Jerusalem (Folder 12)
        - Tel Aviv (Folder 13)
    - Soviet Union
      - China. Chungking Embassy, Reports on (Folder 14)
      - Economy
        - Clippings
          - October (Folder 15)
          - November (Folder 16)
          - December (Folder 17)
        - Monthly reports
          - Sept. (Folder 18)
          - Oct. (Folder 19)
          - Nov. (Folder 20)
          - Nov.-Dec. (Folder 21)
        - Quarterly report, Fourth quarter (Folder 22)
      - Information from various sources (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Polish Embassy in Kuibyshev. Reports (Folder 2)
      - Teheran Legation. Political reports
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
        - October (Folder 6)
        - November (Folder 7)
      - U.S. as Poland's diplomatic representative (Folder 8)
  - 1944
    - Africa. South Africa (Folder 9)
    - America, North
      - Diplomatic representations
        - New York Consulate. Reports (Folder 10)
        - Washington Embassy
          - General (Folder 11)
          - Secret reports
            - Jan.-July (Folder 12)
            - Aug.-Dec. (Folder 13)
      - General Staff. Minority press. Reports (Folder 14)
      - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw. Trip to Moscow. See also SERIES NO. 397
        - General (Folder 15)
        - Harriman, William Averell (Folder 16)
- SERIES NO. 324. PRESS AGENCIES
  Polska Agencja Telegraficzna
  - 1940.
    - General (Folder 17)
    - Brazil (Folder 18)
    - Canada (Folder 19)
    - Finland (Folder 20)
    - Greece (Folder 21)
    - Hungary (Folder 22)
    - Japan (Folder 23)
    - Portugal (Folder 24)
    - Romania (Folder 25)
    - Spain (Folder 26)
    - Sweden (Folder 27)
    - Turkey (Folder 28)
    - Yugoslavia (Folder 29)
  - 1941. Polska Agencja Telegraficzna
    - General (Folder 30)
    - Brazil (Folder 31)
    - Egypt (Folder 32)
    - Finland (Folder 33)
    - Greece (Folder 34)
    - Japan (Folder 35)
    - Palestine (Folder 36)
    - Portugal (Folder 37)
    - Spain (Folder 38)
    - Sweden (Folder 39)
    - Turkey (Folder 40)
    - Yugoslavia (Folder 41)
    - 1942 (Box 173)
    - Katolicka Agencja Prasowa. North America (Folder 1)
    - Polska Agencja Telegraficzna
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Australia (Folder 3)
      - China (Folder 4)
      - Egypt (Folder 5)
      - Palestine (Folder 6)
      - Spain. Aparaty Hela (Folder 7)
      - Sweden (Folder 8)
      - Switzerland (Folder 9)
      - United States (Folder 10)
  - 1943
    - Katolicka Agencja Prasowa
      - Argentina (Folder 11)
      - Ireland (Folder 12)
      - Peru (Folder 13)
      - United States (Folder 14)
    - Overseas News Agency (Folder 15)
    - Polska Agencja Telegraficzna
      - Communiques (Folder 16)
      - Algeria, Correspondent Zygmunt Klingsland in (Folder 17)
      - Brazil (Folder 18)
      - Canada (Folder 19)
      - Egypt (Folder 20)
      - Iran (Folder 21)
      - Mexico (Folder 22)
      - Nyasaland (Folder 23)
      - Palestine (Folder 24)
      - Switzerland (Folder 25)
      - United States (Folder 26)
    - Telegraficheskoe Agentstvo Sovetskovo Soyuza (TASS) (Folder 27)
  - 1944
    - General
      - Foreign press agencies (Folder 28)
      - Polish press agencies (Folder 29)
    - Katolicka Agencja Prasowa
      - Argentina (Folder 30)
      - Brazil (Folder 31)
      - Peru (Folder 32)
      - United States (Folder 33)
    - Polska Agencja Telegraficzna
      - General (Folder 34)
      - Algeria (Folder 35)
      - Australia (Folder 36)
      - Brazil (Folder 37)
      - Canada (Folder 38)
      - China (Folder 39)
      - Egypt (Folder 40)
      - France (Folder 41)
      - Palestine (Folder 42)
      - Sweden (Folder 43)
      - United States (Folder 44)
- SERIES NO. 325. JOURNALS
  - 1940
    - General (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Great Britain. Clippings (Folder 2)
  - 1941
    - Brazil (Folder 3)
    - Canada (Folder 4)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Jestem Polakiem (Folder 6)
    - India (Folder 7)
    - Palestine (Folder 8)
    - Sweden (Folder 9)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 10)
      - List of Polish newspapers published in (Folder 11)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Australia (Folder 13)
    - Brazil (Folder 14)
    - Canada (Folder 15)
    - Cuba (Folder 16)
    - France (Folder 17)
    - Great Britain (Folder 18)
    - India (Folder 19)
    - Iraq (Folder 20)
    - Lithuania (Folder 21)
    - Palestine (Folder 22)
    - Soviet Union (Folder 23)
    - Switzerland (Folder 24)
    - Turkey (Folder 25)
    - United States (Folder 26)
  - 1943
    - Argentina (Folder 27)
    - France (Folder 28)
    - Great Britain (Folder 29)
    - Iran (Folder 30)
    - Kenya (Folder 31)
    - Middle East (Folder 32)
    - Portugal (Folder 33)
    - Soviet Union
      - General (Folder 34)
      - Wolna Polska (Folder 35)
    - Sweden (Folder 36)
    - Switzerland (Folder 37)
    - United States (Folder 38)
  - 1944 (Box 175)
    - Foreign press
      - American (Folder 1)
      - British (Folder 2)
      - French (Folder 3)
      - German (Folder 4)
      - Indian (Folder 5)
      - Soviet (Folder 6)
      - Swiss (Folder 7)
    - Polish press in
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Argentina (Folder 9)
      - Canada (Folder 10)
      - Colombia (Folder 11)
      - Cuba (Folder 12)
      - Great Britain (Folder 13)
      - Palestine (Folder 14)
      - United States (Folder 15)
- SERIES NO. 327. JOURNALISTS AND PUBLICISTS
  - 1940
    - General (Folder 16)
    - Journalists
      - Ciechanowski, Jan (Folder 17)
      - Kleczkowski, Stefan (Folder 18)
      - Nowakowski, Zygmunt (Folder 19)
    - Professional associations. Stowarzyszenie Dziennikarzy i Wydawcow, Toledo, Ohio (Folder 20)
  - 1941
    - General (Folder 21)
    - Journalists
      - Kleczkowski, Stefan (Folder 22)
      - Pendzik, A. (Folder 23)
      - Slonimski, Antoni (Folder 24)
      - Stewart, John (Folder 25)
      - Tarnowski, Antoni
        - General (Folder 26)
        - Publications (Folder 27)
      - Taylor, Henry (Folder 28)
      - Thompson, Dorothy (Folder 29)
      - Tiltman, Hessel (Folder 30)
      - Zbyszewski, W. (Folder 31)
    - Professional associations
      - Association of Jewish Professional Journalists from Poland, Tel Aviv (Folder 32)
      - Union of Polish Journalists, London. List of members (Folder 33)
      - 1942 (Box 176)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Foreign journalists
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Baikalov, Anatol (Folder 3)
      - Butler, Harold (Folder 4)
      - Hershey, Burnet (Folder 5)
      - Turner, Bernard (Folder 6)
    - Polish journalists
      - Fajans, Roman (Folder 7)
      - Kleczkowski, Stefan (Folder 8)
    - Professional associations. Syndykat Dziennikarzy Polskich w Ameryce (Folder 9)
  - 1943
    - Foreign correspondents
      - General
        - General (Folder 10)
        - A-K (Folder 11)
        - L-V (Folder 12)
      - American correspondents
        - General (Folder 13)
        - Dennen, Leon (Folder 14)
        - Hemingway, Martha (Folder 15)
      - Americans and Canadians accredited in
        - London (Folder 16)
        - Moscow (Folder 17)
      - Fredborg, Arrid (Folder 18)
      - Prisoners of war (Folder 19)
    - Polish journalists
      - General (Folder 20)
      - Kleczkowski, Stefan (Folder 21)
    - Professional associations. Syndykat Dziennikarzy Polskich, Stowarzyszenie Wydawcow i Dziennikarzy Polskich. Unification meeting (Folder 22)
  - 1944
    - Foreign correspondents
      - General
        - General (Folder 23)
        - A-K (Folder 24)
        - L-N (Folder 25)
        - P-V (Folder 26)
      - Bernanos, Georges (Folder 27)
      - Finston, Charles (Folder 28)
      - Hemingway, Martha (Folder 29)
      - Kuh, Frederic R. (Folder 30)
      - Lippmann, Walter (Folder 31)
      - Parker, Ralph (Folder 32)
      - Woodside, Wilson (Folder 33)
    - Foreign press. Egypt. Clippings (Folder 34)
    - Polish journalists
      - General, A-Z (Folder 35)
      - Fajans, Roman (Folder 36)
      - Litauer, Stefan (Folder 37)
      - Matuszewski, Ignacy (Folder 38)
      - War correspondents (Folder 39)
    - Professional associations
      - Syndykat Dziennikarzy Polskich (Folder 40)
      - Zwiazek Dziennikarzy Polskich Rzeczypospolitej, London (Folder 41)
- SERIES NO. 331. PUBLICITY IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY
  - 1941
    - General (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - United States. Polski Instytut Naukowy (Folder 2)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 3)
    - United States. Polski Instytut Naukowy (Folder 4)
- SERIES NO. 332. PUBLICITY IN LITERATURE, ARTS, MUSIC, THEATER, OPERA, BALLET, NATIONAL COSTUMES
  - 1940
    - Brazil (Folder 5)
    - Canada (Folder 6)
    - Great Britain (Folder 7)
    - United States (Folder 8)
  - 1941
    - Brazil (Folder 9)
    - Canada (Folder 10)
    - Chile (Folder 11)
    - France (Folder 12)
    - Great Britain (Folder 13)
    - Mexico (Folder 14)
    - United States (Folder 15)
  - 1942
    - Brazil (Folder 16)
    - Canada (Folder 17)
    - Chile (Folder 18)
    - Colombia (Folder 19)
    - Great Britain (Folder 20)
    - Peru (Folder 21)
    - United States (Folder 22)
  - 1943
    - Argentina (Folder 23)
    - Australia (Folder 24)
    - Canada (Folder 25)
    - Chile (Folder 26)
    - Cuba (Folder 27)
    - Great Britain (Folder 28)
    - Iraq
      - General (Folder 29)
      - Posters (Folder 30)
    - Palestine (Folder 31)
    - South Africa (Folder 32)
    - United States (Folder 33)
    - Uruguay (Folder 34)
  - 1944
    - Algeria (Folder 35)
    - Argentina (Folder 36)
    - Brazil (Folder 37)
    - Canada (Folder 38)
    - Egypt (Folder 39)
    - Iran (Folder 40)
    - Ireland (Folder 41)
    - New Zealand (Folder 42)
    - Palestine (Folder 43)
    - Rhodesia (Folder 44)
    - Sweden (Folder 45)
    - Uganda (Folder 46)
    - United States (Folder 47)
- SERIES NO. 333. PUBLICITY IN FILM, SLIDES, AND PHOTOGRAPHY
  - 1940 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - 1941 (Folder 2)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Soviet Union (Folder 4)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 5)
    - United States (Folder 6)
- SERIES NO. 334. PUBLICITY IN RADIO
  - 1940
    - China (Folder 7)
    - Great Britain (Folder 8)
    - Portugal (Folder 9)
    - Spain (Folder 10)
    - United States (Folder 11)
  - 1941
    - General
      - General (Folder 12)
      - Radio (Folder 13)
    - America, South (Folder 14)
    - Argentina (Folder 15)
    - Brazil (Folder 16)
    - Canada (Folder 17)
    - Congo (Folder 18)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Letter from Anthony Eden to Edward Raczynski on conditions of broadcast of Polish radio programs, November 12. Typescript (Folder 20)
    - Middle East (Folder 21)
    - Portugal (Folder 22)
    - Soviet Union. Kosciuszko radio station (Folder 23)
    - United States (Folder 24)
    - Vatican (Folder 25)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 26)
    - Canada (Folder 27)
    - China (Folder 28)
    - Congo (Folder 29)
    - France (Folder 30)
    - Great Britain. B.B.C (Folder 31)
    - Lithuania (Folder 32)
    - Middle East (Folder 33)
    - Soviet Union
      - Kosciuszko radio station (Folder 34)
      - Kuibyshev radio station (Folder 35)
    - United States (Folder 36)
    - Vatican (Folder 37)
    - 1943 (Box 179)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Africa (Folder 2)
    - America, South (Folder 3)
    - Canada (Folder 4)
    - China (Folder 5)
    - Great Britain. B.B.C.
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Government representatives. Speeches (Folder 7)
      - Swit (radio station) (Folder 8)
    - Middle East (Folder 9)
    - Soviet Union
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Kuibyshev radio station (Folder 11)
    - United States (Folder 12)
    - Vatican (Folder 13)
  - 1944
    - General (Folder 14)
    - Africa (Folder 15)
    - America, South (Folder 16)
    - Belgium (Folder 17)
    - Canada (Folder 18)
    - France (Folder 19)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 20)
      - British Broadcasting Corporation (Folder 21)
      - Swit (radio station) (Folder 22)
    - Italy (Folder 23)
    - Middle East (Folder 24)
    - Soviet Union (Folder 25)
    - Sweden (Folder 26)
    - United States (Folder 27)
- SERIES NO. 336. LECTURES
  - 1941
    - Brazil. Lechon, Jan (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Canada
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Brockington, L. W. (Folder 3)
      - Halecki, Oskar (Folder 4)
      - Junosza, Jozef (Folder 5)
    - Chile (Folder 6)
    - Cuba (Folder 7)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Balimski-Jundzill, Jan (Folder 9)
      - Bauer-Czarnomski, F. (Folder 10)
      - Bohdanowicz, L. (Folder 11)
      - Korostowiec (Korostovets), M. (Folder 12)
      - Leitgeber, Boleslaw (Folder 13)
      - Stanczyk, Jan (Folder 14)
      - Westfal, St. (Folder 15)
    - Ireland (Folder 16)
    - New Zealand (Folder 17)
    - South Africa. Lepkowski, S. (Folder 18)
    - Soviet Union (Folder 19)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 20)
      - Arciszewska, Zofia (Folder 21)
      - Aszkenazy, Natalia (Folder 22)
      - Ciechanowski, Jan (Folder 23)
      - Curie, Eva (Folder 24)
      - Friede, Maksymilian (Folder 25)
      - Habsburg, Otto (Folder 26)
  - 1942
    - Brazil (Folder 27)
    - Canada
      - General (Folder 28)
      - Benes, Vojta (Folder 29)
      - Lednicki, Waclaw (Folder 30)
    - Chile (Folder 31)
    - China (Folder 32)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 33)
      - Borenius, Tangred (Folder 34)
      - Prchala, Lew (Folder 35)
      - Stanczyk, Jan (Folder 36)
    - Ireland. Dobrzynski, W. T. (Folder 37)
    - Sweden (Folder 38)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 39)
      - Ciechanowski, Jan (Folder 40)
      - Kwapiszewski, M. (Folder 41)
      - Sokolowski, Wladyslaw (Folder 42)
      - 1943 (Box 181)
    - Algeria (Folder 1)
    - China (Folder 2)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Karski, Jan (Folder 4)
      - Pritt, D. N. (Folder 5)
    - Iraq (Folder 6)
    - South Africa (Folder 7)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Ciechanowski, Jan (Folder 9)
      - Kwapiszewski, M. (Folder 10)
      - Pares, Bernard (Folder 11)
      - Rosenstein-Rodan, P. N. (Folder 12)
      - Sokolowski, Wladyslaw (Folder 13)
      - Sztark, Heliodor (Folder 14)
      - Warfield, G. P. (Folder 15)
      - Welles, Sumner and Adolf Berle (Folder 16)
  - 1944
    - France. Hesch, Hans (Folder 17)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 18)
      - Carr, E. H. (Folder 19)
      - Essex, Morris (Folder 20)
      - Fliess, Walter (Folder 21)
      - International Bureau for the Suppression of Traffic in Women and Children (Folder 22)
      - Kleczkowski, Stefan (Folder 23)
      - Lawrence, P. (Folder 24)
      - Lerski, Jerzy-Jur (Folder 25)
      - Nowakowski, Zygmunt (Folder 26)
      - Russia Today Society (Folder 27)
      - Schaffer, Gordon (Folder 28)
    - Switzerland (Folder 29)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 30)
      - Ciechanowski, Jan (Folder 31)
      - Kazem-Bek, Aleksander, L. (Folder 32)
      - Kerensky, Alexander (Folder 33)
      - Kridl, Manfred (Folder 34)
      - Sztark, Heliodor (Folder 35)
      - Sokolowski, Wladyslaw (Folder 36)
      - Wankowicz, Marta (Folder 37)
- SERIES NO. 337. CELEBRATIONS AND COMMEMORATIONS
  - 1941
    - Argentina (Folder 38)
    - Brazil (Folder 39)
    - Chile (Folder 40)
    - India (Folder 41)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 42)
      - Pulaski Memorial Day (Folder 43)
      - 1942 (Box 182)
    - General
      - Circular (Folder 1)
      - Copernicus Day celebrations (Folder 2)
    - Brazil (Folder 3)
    - Canada (Folder 4)
    - Chile (Folder 5)
    - China (Folder 6)
    - Great Britain (Folder 7)
    - India (Folder 8)
    - Iran (Folder 9)
    - Mexico (Folder 10)
    - Soviet Union (Folder 11)
    - Turkey (Folder 12)
    - United States
      - General
        - Anniversary of German invasion (Folder 13)
        - Grunwald battle celebrations (Folder 14)
      - Consulates
        - Chicago (Folder 15)
        - Detroit (Folder 16)
        - New York (Folder 17)
        - Pittsburgh (Folder 18)
        - San Francisco (Folder 19)
      - U.S. Navy Day (Folder 20)
      - Washington Embassy (Folder 21)
    - Vatican (Folder 22)
    - 1943 (Box 183)
    - General
      - Argentina (Folder 1)
      - Australia (Folder 2)
      - Brazil
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Day of Prayer for Poland (Folder 4)
      - Canada (Folder 5)
      - Chile (Folder 6)
      - China (Folder 7)
      - Great Britain (Folder 8)
      - Egypt (Folder 9)
      - India (Folder 10)
      - Iran (Folder 11)
      - Iraq (Folder 12)
      - Lebanon (Folder 13)
      - Mexico (Folder 14)
      - New Zealand (Folder 15)
      - Nyasaland (Folder 16)
      - Palestine (Folder 17)
      - Peru (Folder 18)
      - Sweden (Folder 19)
      - United States
        - General (Folder 20)
        - Chiang Kai-shek's trip to (Folder 21)
        - Pulaski Day (Folder 22)
      - Uruguay (Folder 23)
      - Vatican (Folder 24)
    - Anniversary of German invasion
      - General. Instructions and circulars (Folder 25)
      - Algeria (Folder 26)
      - Brazil (Folder 27)
      - Canada (Folder 28)
      - Great Britain (Folder 29)
      - Chile (Folder 30)
      - China (Folder 31)
      - Cuba (Folder 32)
      - Iran (Folder 33)
      - Iraq (Folder 34)
      - Kenya (Folder 35)
      - Lebanon (Folder 36)
      - Peru (Folder 37)
      - Portugal (Folder 38)
      - South Africa (Folder 39)
      - Sweden (Folder 40)
      - United States (Folder 41)
      - Uruguay (Folder 42)
    - Copernicus Day (Box 184)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Brazil (Folder 2)
      - Canada (Folder 3)
      - Chile (Folder 4)
      - China (Folder 5)
      - Cuba (Folder 6)
      - India (Folder 7)
      - Peru (Folder 8)
      - South Africa (Folder 9)
      - United States (Folder 10)
    - Independence Day
      - Argentina (Folder 11)
      - Brazil (Folder 12)
      - Canada (Folder 13)
      - Chile (Folder 14)
      - China (Folder 15)
      - Cuba (Folder 16)
      - Czechoslovakia (Folder 17)
      - Egypt (Folder 18)
      - Great Britain (Folder 19)
      - Iraq (Folder 20)
      - Peru (Folder 21)
      - Rhodesia (Folder 22)
      - South Africa (Folder 23)
      - Sweden (Folder 24)
      - Tanganyika (Folder 25)
      - United States (Folder 26)
    - May 3rd celebration
      - Africa (Folder 27)
      - Brazil (Folder 28)
      - Canada (Folder 29)
      - Chile (Folder 30)
      - China (Folder 31)
      - India (Folder 32)
      - Peru (Folder 33)
      - Turkey (Folder 34)
      - United States (Folder 35)
    - Polish Children Day
      - General. Circulars (Folder 36)
      - Africa
        - General (Folder 37)
        - South Africa (Folder 38)
      - America
        - North
          - Canada (Folder 39)
          - United States (Folder 40)
        - South (Folder 41)
      - Asia (Folder 42)
      - Europe (Folder 43)
      - Middle East (Folder 44)
      - New Zealand (Folder 45)
      - 1944 (Box 185)
    - General
      - Belgium (Folder 1)
      - Brazil (Folder 2)
      - Canada (Folder 3)
      - Chile (Folder 4)
      - Great Britain (Folder 5)
      - Haiti (Folder 6)
      - Iran (Folder 7)
      - Lebanon (Folder 8)
      - Palestine (Folder 9)
      - United States
        - General (Folder 10)
        - Pulaski Day (Folder 11)
    - Anniversary of German invasion
      - Algeria (Folder 12)
      - Argentina (Folder 13)
      - Brazil (Folder 14)
      - Chile (Folder 15)
      - Colombia (Folder 16)
      - Congo (Folder 17)
      - Cuba (Folder 18)
      - Egypt (Folder 19)
      - Great Britain
        - General (Folder 20)
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw. Speech to Poland and declaration to press (Folder 21)
      - India (Folder 22)
      - Iraq (Folder 23)
      - Peru (Folder 24)
      - Portugal (Folder 25)
      - South Africa (Folder 26)
      - Tanganyika (Folder 27)
      - United States (Folder 28)
      - Uruguay (Folder 29)
    - Copernicus Day (Folder 30)
    - Independence Day
      - General (Folder 31)
      - Algeria (Folder 32)
      - Argentina (Folder 33)
      - Brazil (Folder 34)
      - Canada (Folder 35)
      - China (Folder 36)
      - Great Britain (Folder 37)
      - India (Folder 38)
      - Rhodesia (Folder 39)
      - Tanganyika (Folder 40)
      - United States (Folder 41)
      - Vatican (Folder 42)
    - May 3rd celebration (Box 186)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Africa, North (Folder 2)
      - Brazil (Folder 3)
      - Canada (Folder 4)
      - Chile (Folder 5)
      - Colombia (Folder 6)
      - Cuba (Folder 7)